Another day with no activity
from Gekko, I see.
Seriously.
They've been keeping their heads
down these past two weeks.
But at least we get a little peace and quiet!
Wait a minute.
You're not allowed to stack draw cards!
It's legal where I come from!
Yes... peace is best.
No, it's cheating!
No one wants to fight if they don't have to.
However...
If I don't fight, I won't
be able to see Desumi-san!
Fudo~
Fudo!
MUSCLE
Use my weight training
regimen to reach the top!
I haven't had a proper night's sleep in weeks.
Fudo
Fudo!
I'm going through serious
Desumi-san withdrawal!
Fudo
Fudo...
I have to do something about this!
Signs of new weapon development
in Gekko's headquarters detected.
I repeat, signs of new weapon development
Speak of the devil!
The team is to infiltrate their base
and destroy the new weapon!
An infiltration mission, eh?
This isn't going to be easy.
That's way too dangerous!
It's basically suicide!
But someone has to do it!
Pink and Blue are traveling.
Green is on paid leave.
It has to be either you
or Fudo-kun, Misaki-kun!
And the other needs to remain here,
just in case something happens.
All right. I'll go—
I'll go!
Fudo-kun?!
Hang on! Don't you realize
how dangerous this is?
I will go!
No...
I must go!
But...
Misaki-kun...
Try to understand him!
He knows... He knows what he's doing!
Freezing Change!
One!
Change Gelato!
Red Gelato, Fudo Aikawa, departing!
Fudo!
You'd better come back, you hear me?!
He really is stupid.
He is a true hero!
And now I'll get...
to see Desumi-san!
Episode 3     At Last, the Amusement Park
Pay respect to the Reaper Princess!
Welcome, Reaper Princess!
Dang, she's in a killer mood today.
She seems even more murderous than usual!
Bet she woke up on the wrong side of the bed!
No, that's not what this is.
I'm actually in agony.
Because...
I haven't seen Fudo in two whole weeks!
Desumi-san
Desumi-san!
Desumi-san... Desumi-san...
Excuse me, combatants...
M-Ma'am!
When do you think we'll get
to fight those heroes again?
She's out for blood!
We do not know! Please forgive us!
Er, that's okay... I'm sorry.
I had a lousy horoscope this morning, too.
L
E
O
You won't see the person
you're waiting for.
Lucky Item
Pouch
Today's worst horoscope
goes to you, my Leo friends!
D
O
M
.
You won't see the person you're waiting for.
Your lucky item is a cute little pouch!
Guess it didn't do any good.
Ah, Reaper Princess!
Culverin Bear-sama...
Behold! It's finished at last!
My new weapons, the Neo Culverin Cannons!
I'll use my new power
to atomize those heroes!
That's quite a dangerous
thing you've got there, too.
What?
It's just a pouch—
Say no more. I know exactly what it is.
It holds concealed weapons!
Well, actually—
And the pouch's design is camouflage
to get the enemy's guard down!
You're a terrifying woman, start to finish!
Maybe I'm just not a good fit for this stuff.
Fu—
Desumi-san!
I've been looking everywhere.
I've missed you!
Fudo...
I... I'm so happy to see you, too!
Wait, no!
What do you think you're doing?!
Reaper Princess
Dressing Room
Ah!
So this is your dressing room?!
It's as girly as I expected!
What were you thinking, Fudo?
This is extremely dangerous!
I just wanted to see you that badly!
Well, I... I wanted to see you, too...
But this is still way too dangerous—
I know, Desumi!
You want to play this with me?
This.
Y-Yes.
Professor, any word from Fudo?
No, nothing yet.
I see...
For now, all we can do is have faith.
There! I win!
And now for your punishment!
Hold out your hand!
If you insist.
Here I go!
Your hand's so nice and warm.
Don't say that! Now I can't do it!
Oh so cute...
I have a report!
Rea...per Prin...
...cess. It appears there's
an intruder in the base!
We need to be on high alert!
I'm aware of the situation.
Let's remain cautious.
E-Excuse me...
I felt sure I saw a man there just—
Your imagination, I'm sure.
Yeah, I'll bet!
It's not like you'd ever be
with a man, Reaper Princess!
Farewell!
S-Sorry, Fudo!
Are you all right?!
I'm coming in, Reaper—
—Prin...cess...
There's an intruder—
Oh, she's not here?
D-Desumi-san?
Oh, no...
I accidentally shut myself in with you!
W-Well...
It's kind of a tight fit.
Stupid! Stop moving around!
And there's something on my face
that's making it hard to breathe.
I really need to take it off.
I got it off!
New weapon signal lost!
Damage to Gekko's base confirmed as well!
Did he do it?!
Fudo, you're amazing!
Sorry to just drop in on
you like that, Desumi-san.
No, I'm the one who should apologize.
You came all that way to see me,
and I was a terrible host.
Oh... Fudo, there's a cut on your cheek.
Hey, it's all right.
Come down here a minute.
That should do it!
Thank you, Desumi-san.
Hey, what a cute pouch!
It's perfect for you!
And... I wish I'd thought
of this earlier, but...
Here. It's my phone number.
Now we can talk any time we want to!
Hey, Fudo...
Is it okay if I call you tonight?
Bluuush
Oh so cute...
Yes, of course!
Secret Society Gekko
Women's Dorm
C-Calm down.
You're okay.
You're just calling to make
sure he got home safe.
A-All right!
Yes? Aikawa residence!
Mom, that call's for me!
What are you doing here, Fudo?
I told you to go out and buy milk!
Just give me the phone!
Sorry, Desumi-san. It's me.
Who is it?
Who is it?!
Fudo...
Please buy a smartphone.
Yes, that might be best.
Love After World Domination!
Good morning.
It's time for the morning meeting.
All executives, please
come to the meeting room.
Good morning, all!
I am Supreme Leader Bosslar.
Head of Secret Society Gekko
Supreme Leader Bosslar
I believe it's time to begin
our regular meeting.
Your brave efforts have allowed us to
collect a steady supply of negative energy.
Rejoice!
The birth of our monstrous culmination,
Ultimate Phantom, is at hand!
Allow me to explain!
Secret Society Gekko,
led by Supreme Leader Bosslar,
Negative
Negative Energy
uses the negative emotions
of humans as a power source,
to create new monsters,
Ultimate Phantom
and further its goal of world domination!
In the interest of collecting the
remaining negative energy needed,
I will now take suggestions
regarding our next target.
Beast Princess
Yes, Beast Princess?
Who the hell cares what our target is?
Beast Princess
Gekko Princess Series
Just let us fight already!
But the selection of the target
is the purpose of this meeting.
You're as boorish as ever.
Steel Princess
Yes, Steel Princess?
Gekko Princess Series
Steel Princess
I require more time to consider the matter.
You didn't need to press the button for that!
Heat Princess
Yes, Heat Princess.
Gekko Princess Series
Heat Princess
Say something already!
This is ridiculous.
Doesn't anyone have a real suggestion?!
Excellent! Reaper Princess!
A view of the city lights.
Reaper Princess
That's far too abstract.
Next—
An aquarium.
It's difficult to fight indoors.
An amusement park!
What's with you and date destinations?!
Disappointment...
Wait a moment, Bosslar-sama!
An amusement park would be filled
with helpless, unsuspecting humans!
And we could have our fill, you mean?
That's a nasty little brain
you've got, Reaper Princess.
Very well.
Our next target shall
be... the amusement park!
Smartphones for Dummies!
Learn it all in just 10 minutes!
You have a new message
I'm still not used to that sound.
Desumi-san
Big Gelato
It's from Desumi-san!
Fudo! Rejoice!
Gekko's next target is that theme park
we've been wanting to go to, Yomiuriland!
Wh-What?!
I don't mind meeting up in old factories
and quarries and places like that...
But I wish we could go to a proper
couples' spot once in a while.
I agree. Like an aquarium!
Or a place with a view of the city lights!
A theme park would be awesome, too!
Of course, that's all a distant dream.
I can't believe that dream of a few
days ago is coming true for us already!
The attack will be Sunday, three days from now
Can't wait!
Desumi-san leaks her organization's
deepest-held secrets so casually.
That sweet little scatterbrain...
squee
Okay, I'd better reply!
What? "Swipe"?!
Look at him fret!
What in the world is he doing?
He apparently got his first
smartphone yesterday.
Fudo got a smartphone?!
That bodybuilding gremlin got a smartphone?!
Impossible!
Hey, Suri!
Um... I... I'll come to the... like
to come to... theme thark... Thunday.
W-Weather?! Tell me... t-tell
weather. To me, please.
I didn't catch that.
Something's going down here!
Fudo! Did you think you could hide from
the mistress of meddling, Misaki?!
I can't wait until Sunday!
All right! Disguise complete!
Now, let's get to the bottom
of our little Fudo's secret!
Good Mesh Cap
&
Good Towel
We really shouldn't stalk
him like this, Misaki-san.
I really don't think he's hiding anything.
If that's the way you feel,
why'd you tag along?
I j-just want to stop you
from doing anything reckless!
Awesome! It's Red!
So cool!
It's really him!
What're you doing?
Patrolling.
Are you fighting Gekko?
I don't know yet.
But if anything happens,
get to that shelter over there.
Just remain calm, and do not panic.
Okay!
See? Look at that!
He's patrolling, just like he always does!
He's devoted to world peace,
just like I thought!
Well, we'll see.
I mean, he's still a guy.
Darn it!
How?!
How are there heroes here now?
Not just Red, but Pink and Yellow...
Did they know we'd be here somehow?
They don't leave us a choice.
Indeed. We'll have to retreat
for now and regroup—
If they know we're here,
we'll just have to fight!
They don't know we're here yet, stupid!
There you are, Desu—
I mean, Reaper Princess!
You really kept me waiting, Fudo—
I mean, Red!
Freezing Change!
One!
Change Gelato!
The aroma of strawberry,
the flavor of justice!
Red Gelato!
Awesome!
Now, everyone! Get to safety!
smack
I see you tracked us down, Gelato 5!
Did he really just come here
because he knew they'd attack?
Well, didn't I tell you?
Fudo-senpai isn't hiding anything!
I guess you're right.
Freezing Change!
Three!
Four!
Yellow Gelato!
Pink Gelato!
Let's call for help from Blue and Green!
Roger!
Senpai!
We came to back you up!
No! Stay back!
Don't worry about me!
I'm a hero, too!
You were totally right, Haru!
Fudo's the guy he's always been!
Right!
So honest and straightforward.
Forthright and earnest in everything he does!
That's our leader!
Here...
Here.
Sounds great...
Sounds great!
Hero Training Center
Wh-What is it?
You're certainly talkative
when the subject is Fudo!
H-Hey! I am not!
I didn't think rides would
give you motion sickness.
I didn't know either, until today.
There's not even that
much motion. I'm pathetic.
D-Don't rock the car!
Desumi-san?
I was just thinking... getting to know
these hidden sides of each other...
It's kind of nice, Fudo.
Desumi-san...
Feeling a little better now?
Yes.
How mysterious.
I was so uncomfortable
on this ride until now...
But now, I hope I never
touch the ground again.
Look, Fudo! It seems the battle's over.
You're right.
We'd better get back.
I think we might've crossed a line today.
The theme park is a fearsome place.
Come feel the thrill with us again!
So much shopping!
I'm so glad the guys are here
to help me carry everything.
You bought way too much.
Fudo-senpai?
Hello? Haruta-san?
Listen to this!
My boy bought me a dinosaur keychain
from an amusement park he went to!
Honestly, that boy!
He never seems to grow up.
Now, on to the main topic!
He says episode 4 will be called
"Could You Please Tell Me Why?"
Episode 4     Could You Please Tell Me Why?
Who's "Haruta-san"?